我首先想说的是
I'd like to begin by saying
白宫媒体简报会
今天大家关注的唯一焦点就是
there is only one thing on anybody's mind today...
总统主持了她的首次国际来访
The president's hosting of her first state visit.
在友好迎接了以色列总理到达白宫之后...
After welcoming the Israeli Prime Minister to the White House...
他染了胡子吗?
Did he dye his mustache?
以确保他们掌握了...
To ensure that they seize this...
我了个大槽 他染了胡子
Holy shit, he dyed his mustache.
面子工程啊 他是行政部门的脸面
It's vanity. He's the TV face of the administration.
脸上粘了虾条似的
But he's glued Cheetos to that face.
以为自己扮张飞
He looks like Yosemite Sam.
是哦 还没人家的架势
Yeah, without the credibility.
下一步他就该把奶头染成小粉红了
He's gonna get his tits done next.
- Sean? -今天是总统就职第33天
- Sean? - Today's the president's 33rd day in office.
她会比威廉·亨利·哈里森 那个有史以来任职最短的总统 干得久些么
She's outlasted William Henry Harrison, our shortest serving president.
(就任满一月病逝)
-她感觉怎么样? -她感觉好极了
- How's she feel about that? - She feels great,
和那个在就职演讲时染上了肺炎
unlike President Harrison who contracted pneumonia
就死了哈里森总统完全不同
during his inaugural address and died.
感谢各位
Thanks, ladies and gentlemen.
干得漂亮啊 Mike 火力全开啊
Nice work, Mike. You're on fire.
哦 不对 是你的胡子红似火
Nope, wait. It's your mustache.
我叫这个橘色幻梦（德国电子音乐先驱团体的名字）
I call it Tangerine Dream.
等会儿去喝点儿么
Hey, are we getting cocktails later?
啊 不行啊 我得回家
No, I can't. I've got to get home.
你...
You...
-你能想到我说这个吗? -不 喝酒咱最爱
- Can you imagine? - No. We love to drink.
所以 我们重点考虑是家庭第一提案的辩论环节
So our concern is debate time for Families First.
竞选会议 罗斯福室
规则委员会的朋友们需要被狠狠推一把
Our friends on the rules committee need a shove.
所以你想让我来管理白宫规则委员会
So you want me to rule the House rules committee.
对 我有信心 你就是能干这个的人
Yeah, if anyone can do this, Dan, I'm confident
或是那个我们雇来取代你位子的人也能干
you or the guy we hired to replace you can.
这次以色列来访真是让我激动啊
I am really excited about this Israeli visit.
今天是个好日子 伙计们
Gonna be a good day, guys.
中东 中容易
Middle East, middle easy.
我想谈一下晚宴摆件的问题
I'm a little concerned about the dinner centerpieces,
-因为我觉得他们...-随便啦
- 'cause I feel like they...- Whatever.
我在这儿维护世界和平呢 好吗?
I'm handling world peace, okay?
你只需要把那房间弄得漂漂亮亮的就成
You just go make the room pretty,
比如说 和那个畸形相反的东西
i.e., the opposite of that fucking monstrosity.
那啥玩意? 毕加索的大姨妈汹涌澎湃?
What is that? Picasso's heavy period?
-前总统喜欢这个 -所以他老婆想自杀么?
- President Hughes loved it. - Is that why his wife tried to kill herself?
我想这叫 一个男人菊吐三角
I think it's called "A Man Who Shits Triangles."
屁股里面塞着五角(大楼)已经够受的了
Bad enough having the Pentagon up your ass.
Amy哪去了?
Where is Amy, by the way?
她身为竞选经理 而这是个竞选大会
She's campaign manager, this is a campaign meeting.
我是说 我还要去拯救世界呢
I mean, I've got to go save the world.
我知道这听起来有点吹牛逼 但是
I know that sounds like hyperbole, but...
-但是你就是要去 -我就是要去拯救世界
- But you do. Yeah. - I do, in fact.
我还真是要去拯救世界呢
I actually do do have to do that.
我刚收到Amy的短信
I just got a text from Amy.
我会痴点
"I'm a latte"?
-啥? -猜她想说她会迟点
- Huh? - Guess she means she's late.
你还说不会堵车
You said there wouldn't be traffic.
-现在就堵车了 -是啊
- This is traffic. - Yep.
任何原因都有可能...交通事故啊 持枪乱扫啊
Could be anything... accident up ahead, active shooter.
估计不是那个吧
Well, probably not that.
你要是再敢害我迟到 我就把你锁在车里 再把这辆车压成小方块
You make me any more late, and I lock you in this car and have it compacted.
-来点音乐吧 -表
- How about some music? Hmm? - No.
我把你手机接上蓝牙了 所以..
I Bluetoothed your phone, so...
个人记事 我能赢
Memo to self... it is winnable.
-取消个人投票 - 我要把它关了
- Delete the private polling. - Oh, turn that off.
我想我连上音乐播放器了呢
I thought I had it on shuffle.
脱毛
Also, hair.
问Marianne电解脱毛的事
Ask Marianne about electrolysis.
这次选举 整个宣传策略
The campaign, the whole comm strategy.
我们现在出了太多篓子了
We've got too many balls being dropped right now.
比方说 我们又得到了一张
For instance, we've got yet another
关于Catherine的可怕图片
appalling photograph of Catherine.
没有恶意啊亲爱的 但是你看看你这张脸
No offense, honey, but, I mean, look at yourself.
这不是我的错 这家媒体就把我当回事
It's not my fault. The press doesn't take me seriously
因为我在这儿没地位
because I don't have a role here.
我需要成为核心成员
I need a core role.
对 这是个非常好的主意
Yeah, that's a very good idea.
她有很棒的组织能力
She has good organizational skills.
-她把校园电影社团搅得天翻地覆 -我是让它脱胎换骨 老妈
- She turned around the college film society. - I transformed it, Mom.
她..她...干的漂亮
She... she... good for you.
夫人 我弄了个虚拟Amy
Ma'am, I've got a virtual Amy.
夫人  我很抱歉
Ma'am, I am so sorry.
噢 她就不能只打电话来么
Oh, can't she just call in?
我觉得我穿越到未来了
I feel like I'm on trial in the future.
夫人 如果我能打断一下的话 我真的认为...
Ma'am, if I could interrupt. I really think that...
Amy啊 信号不好 你说一个字漏一个字呢
Uh, Amy, it's filtering out like every other word.
通常我自己这么干
Usually I just do that myself.
好的 所以我们需要Bill Ericsson来稳住大局
Okay, this is why we need asteady hand like Bill Ericsson.
顺便一提 我会让Bill Ericsson加入
By the way, I'm bringing in Bill Ericsson.
总统夫人 你刚刚是说Bill Ericsson吗?
Madam President, did you just say Bill Ericsson?
夫人 我..噢!
Ma'am, I... Ooh!
好了好了 真是不忍直视
Oh, okay, I can't look at that anymore.
看Mike的胡子已经够我受的了
It's bad enough looking at Mike's mustache.
你看到他的胡子了? 跟吃了个火山似得
Have you seen that thing? It's like he ate a volcano.
夫人 我们这还有些国家安全方面的事情
Ma'am, we do have that issue of national security,
所以我想现在Catherine...
so I'm afraid that Catherine right now...
好 Catherine 亲爱的 你必须出去了
Oh, okay. Catherine, you have to get out, honey.
-走吧 -对不起了哈
- Go.- Sorry, I apologize.
总统夫人 我想说的是
Madam President, I'd like to state
Catherine是很有价值的成员
that I think that Catherine is a valuable asset.
-对 -也是您的女儿
- Yeah. - And daughter.
但是她的受欢迎指数
But her likability index is...
非常之低
shallow.
啥?
What?
我们对她的欢迎程度进行了投票
We polled her popularity.
你竟敢?
How dare you?
你哪来的胆子竟然...
How could you have the audacity to...
哦
Oh.
这看起来不妙啊
Oh, these are not good.
好吧 得有人告诉她这个
Okay, well, she's gonna have to be told.
当然了 温柔点
Gently, of course.
但是谁去告诉她呢?
But who's going to do that?
-夫人 我相信我可以 -那就是你了
- I believe I have the skills, ma'am. - There you go.
好 Kent 你去做
Fine. You do it, Kent.
好的.. 怎么了?
Okay... what?
夫人 今天是个特别的日子哟
Ma'am, today is a very special day.
我知道 我正在引领和平的道路
I know. I'm building a road map to peace.
不仅如此 夫人 不仅如此
Not just that, ma'am. Not just that.
别告诉我今天是哈里森日(就任满一月)
Don't tell me it's Happy Harrison Day.
我比某个蠢货死总统干的要久了 哇哦
I outlived some dead idiot president. Wow.
不
No.
-啥? -今天是Ben的生日
- What? - It's Ben's birthday.
-哦!- 我生日
- Oh! - My birthday.
生日快乐 Ben
Happy birthday, Ben.
-这么快就到了啊 -是啊
- Wow, that was quick. - Yeah.
-我们有蛋糕吃吗 -没有
- We have a cake? - No.
没有?
No?
好吧 打岔打得漂亮啊
All right, well, that was a good interruption.
谢谢
Thanks.
不 不 不 不 不 不 不
No, no, no. No, no, no.
啊 威廉·亨利·哈里森
Ah, William Henry Harrison.
哦 老天 终于有个人
Oh, God, at least somebody...
注意到这个奇葩蛋糕吗
Noticed this horrible cake?
不用谢
You're welcome.
往前走吧
Just go ahead.
嗨 Jonah
Hey, Jonah.
你好 嗨 你好 先生
Hello. Hi. Hello, sir.
最好想个主意讨我欢心啊
Better think of a way to make me feel good.
好 必须的
Okay, of course.
我给你拿点薯片 或者...
I could go get you some Pringles or...
Teddy非常认可你
Teddy done you a solid.
在我的建议下 副总统将让你参加
On my advice, the veep's gonna ask you to be
Dan Egan进行的关于家庭第一提案说客行动
in the Families First talks with Dan Egan.
哦 这消息太棒了 先生
Oh, that's fantastic news, sir.
你这么一说就立刻成全了我的好日子而毁了他的
You simultaneously made my day and ruined his.
谢谢 雄起哦
Thank you. Shine brightly.
起 起 起 起 起 起 起
Tap-tap-tap-tap-tap-tap.
没啥问题吧
All good?
- 没问题 -没问题
- Yeah. Yeah.- Yeah?
你看 晚宴需要一个更大的桌面摆件
See, we need bigger centerpieces for the state dinner tonight.
不在乎花多少钱 你来跟进一下
I don't care about the cost. You got to get on that.
听着 请听着
Listen, please, please, please.
如果有人不知道
If anybody doesn't know the difference
小帷幔和长领花的区别的的话 就可以离开了好吗
between a valance and a jabot, I really need you to leave.
总统的造型师收到我的备注了么? -收到了
- Did the president's stylist get my notes? - Yes, he did.
好 太好了 哦天啊
Okay, thank God. Oh, my God.
这是从流浪汉的坟头扒来的么
Did we get these from a homeless man's grave?
刺瞎我的眼睛! 这里到底是怎么的了?
They're molesting my eyes. What's happening right now?
-我最喜欢的人儿在这儿呢 -Patty!
- There's my favorite guy. - Patty!
我最爱的白宫社交秘书!
My favorite White House social secretary!
你听说了桌上摆件的事了么?
Did you hear about the centerpieces?
听说了 我听说你把它退了 让它装饰地狱去了
I did. I heard you sent them back to centerpiece hell.
就是说啊 我们觉得那就是不对头
I know. We felt they weren't right.
所以 这是总统的意见?
So this is coming from the president?
这是我们的意见
It's coming from us.
还有那个画 她也不想要了吗?
And the painting, she wants that swapped out, too?
对 我们是这么想的
Yes, we do.
你说那个桌上摆件不对头
And when you say that the centerpieces are not right,
你能给我稍微说说
can you just give me a little indication
是怎么个不对头么
of what you mean when you say "not right"?
我们就是觉得吧 那需要有个不一样的形状
We just kind of feel like they need to be a different shape.
-要特别突出 -好的
- They need to pop. - Okay.
-好 要突出? -突出
- Okay, they need to pop? - Pop.
-哦 我听见你说的了 -好
- No, I heard you. - Okay.
-好 -找到一个懂我们的人真是太好了
- Okay. - It is so good to find someone who gets us.
-恩 -真的特别好
- Mm. - It really is.
Sue 我现在需要见总统
Sue, I need to see the president right away.
好的 Amy 我就去告诉以色列人让他们让让 因为他们就喜欢这样
Sure, Amy, I'll just tell the Israelis to move on, 'cause they love that.
好吧 Richard 你得把Ben的安定藏起来
All right, Richard, you need to hide Ben's Ativan
直到他把Bill Ericsson的事全坦白了
till he comes clean about Bill Ericsson.
-嗨 Amy -Bill 见..见到你真好啊
- Hi, Amy. - Bill, it... it's good to see you.
-我听说你在...-在白宫工作 对的
- I hear you're working... - Working at the White House. Yes, I am.
-什么职位? -什么职位?
- In what capacity? - What capacity?
我有一个特别的头衔 不过管得很宽
I have a specific title, but a wide brief...
消除弱点
Eliminate weaknesses.
有点儿纳粹医生的感觉
That's a little Nazi doctor.
我是传媒部门的新领导
I'm the new director of communications.
哦 不错啊 因为某些人以为
Oh, that's cool, 'cause some of us thought
你是新的竞选经理呢
you were the new campaign manager.
-嗯! -哦 不 我懂了 好的
- Mmm! - Oh, no. I get it. Okay.
好吧 我只是想用不那么友好的方式友好的打个招呼
Well, I just wanted to say a friendly hello in an unfriendly way.
你好
Hello.
好的 我试着发音标准些
Okay, I'm gonna try to say it right.
Shalom aleichem.
-说得非常好 -美国欢迎您
- Aleichem. Very good. - And welcome to America.
感谢您的热情迎接
Thank you very much for your hospitality.
好了 我不是想打岔
All right, I don't mean to be abrupt,
但是到此为止吧 谢谢
but this is over. Thank you.
所以我们休息五分钟 然后继续?
So I think we have a five-minute break and then we can resume, yes?
-好 非常好 - 好 棒极了 谢谢
- Okay, very well. - Okay, wonderful. Thank you.
我喜欢他 我可讨厌政客了
I like him. And I loathe politicians.
总统女士 白宫的一幅画今天被移除了
Madam President, a painting in theWhite House was removed this morning.
所以我们就要躲去战情室了?
Should we go to the Situation Room?
这是整栋大楼里唯一的印第安人艺术品
It was the only work of art by a Native American artist in the building.
我是说 谁知道我们有那个啊
I mean, who knew we even had one?
那个画了些发癫的三角形的画
It was the crazy triangles painting.
印第安人觉得他们收到了怠慢
Native Americans are taking it as a slight, ma'am.
那就发个申明说我们只是把它送出去清洗
Then just issue a statement saying we had it sent out to be cleaned.
对了 让Bill Ericsson做这件事
Actually, have Bill Ericsson do that
因为我打算让Bill Ericsson取代你
because I'm having Bill Ericsson replace you.
-总统女士? -什么?
- Madam President? - Yeah?
关于缩减封锁一致性可行性
Points of departure for the possible agreements
的实时讨论报告
on the scale-down of blockades.
那是谁?
Who is that?
老实说 我都不知道她是不是我们的人
To be honest, I don't even know if she's one of ours.
20刀打赌她叫Mossad 行了 我们只有4分钟了
20 bucks says she's Mossad. Come on, we've only got four minutes.
好 对不起 Jim 我没空
Okay. Sorry, Jim. I don't have time
来跟你解释我对那个的想法
to explain my thinking on that.
我脑子里都是中东的事呢
It's just I've got the Middle East in here.
即使我们有些观点不同
Even though we have our differences,
我认为我妈妈推动和平谈判这事
I think my mom brokering major peace talks
非常的了不起
is super awesome.
真的是 非常了不起
It is. Super awesome.
我想跟你谈些私人问题
But I want to talk to you about a more personal matter.
我没跟那些家伙吸毒
I didn't take drugs with those guys.
我只是在他们的大巴里呆了半个小时
I was just in their bus for half an hour.
知道也好
That is good to know.
这是Catherine Meyer形象品牌问题
This is about the brand image of Catherine Meyer, TM.
我让你来是因为
I asked you in because, um...
Catherine 美国不喜欢你
Catherine, America doesn't like you.
啥？
What?
这听起来太残酷了点
That sounded way too harsh
头版标题版的总结词
when boiled down to a headline thought.
-给我看看 -这并不代表你不讨人喜欢
- Let me see that. - It's not that you are unlikable.
只是一种观点说你不讨人喜欢
It's that there's a perception that you are unlikable.
他们恨我
They hate me.
我不会用恨这个词 你只是
I wouldn't say hate. You just...
两极化的观点 而这一头比较重
polarize opinion with the bulk of it gravitating to this pole here.
呃 哦 天啊
Uh... oh, my.
你肩膀挺削的
You have sharp shoulders.
这就像是高中重演
This is like high school all over again.
对 有点儿吧 规模更大了
Yeah, sure, kind of, but much bigger.
让我们来谈谈转变你的形象的问题吧
So let's talk about changing your narrative.
得到公众认可的捷径有
Customary shortcuts to public affirmation
服役或者生孩子
are military service or childbirth.
好吧 天啊 才不 老天爷啊 我才不 照你说的那样做
Okay, God, no, and, oh, my God, no, in that order.
好吧 让我们回到想办法转变
Okay, well, then we go back to the idea
这张苦脸
of turning that frown
成为不苦脸的问题上
into the inverse of a frown.
-扭转乾坤？ -如果你愿意的话
- Upside down? - If you will.
所以你从来都没有想过
So there wasn't even like a little part of you
我会加入谈话？
that thought I was gonna be in these talks?
好了 你看 你就坐在那里听我指挥
Okay, look, just sit there in the meeting and let me take the lead.
如果我需要你帮助 我会给你个信号
If I need your help, I'll give you a signal.
好 啥信号？
Okay, what's the signal?
没有啥信号 Jonah
There's not gonna be a signal, Jonah.
-嗨 - Pierce议员 见到你很高兴
- Hey. - Congressman Pierce, so good to see you.
嗨 小培根你抖个啥? 这是我打招呼的方式 活络下气氛
Hey, what's shakin', bacon? That's my way of saying hello, breaking the ice.
-天 见到你真好 -这是我同事
- God, it's good to see you. - This is my colleague.
-让我们开始吧 -好嘞
- But you know what? Let's get started. - Yeah.
我喜欢你的办公室 这真棒
I really like your office. This is a great office.
你布置家具的方式
The way you've arranged the furniture.
这个骑马的人 那个画
This horse guy over here, that painting.
这是我来过的最棒的办公室了
This is the nicest office I've ever been in.
我这位朋友挺兴奋的
My friend here is very excited here,
就好像我们都为这个家庭第一提案兴奋一样
as are we, obviously, about the Families First bill.
特别是 这个先期K计划
Specifically, the pre-K program
特别针对低收入家庭 我们极力推崇这部分
for low-income families. We're very proud of that.
我所代表的人民
Well, the people that I represent
喜欢看到钱花的很明智
like to see that money is spent wisely.
当然了 所以我们一直提倡不能穷教育
Of course, that's why we always say invest in education.
你懂得 不要只把他们当孩子
You know, don't think of them as kids
而要当成小人形创业公司
as much as little human start-ups.
你懂的 花钱即是存钱
You know, spend to save.
然后你就可以把你存的钱拿出来花了
And then you take the money you save and you spend it.
这就是经济学
That's economics.
好吧 在我的桌上
And, well, on my desk here,
你看我存了一盒优惠券
you see I keep a box of coupons.
我自己剪的哦
I clip them myself.
这时刻提醒我记得勤俭节约
And this is to help me to remember to be economical.
真是个好主意
That is a fantastic idea.
我这就记下来 我也要这么干
I'm gonna take a page. I'm gonna do this myself.
你知道这里面好些都过期了么
Did you know that a lot of these have expired?
对 我非常 特别忙...
Yeah, I'm so... It's so busy on the...
-我在忙规则委员会的事情 -当然了
- I'm on the rules committee now. - Of course.
所以你是说理论上你支持这项提案
So what you're saying is that you support the bill in principle,
但是会担心支出的增长
but you're worried that an escalation of cost
会让你白宫的同僚们不满意?
wouldn't sit well with your colleagues in the House?
恩..这 ..这总结的挺好
Mmm, that's... yeah, that's very well put.
-谢谢 -嗨 你喜欢打保龄球么?
- Thank you. - Hey, you like to bowl?
哦 我打的不好
Oh, I am a terrible bowler.
但是我特别喜欢用它做些社交活动
But I enjoy the social aspects immensely.
你知道吗 我们明天晚上有个小聚会
Well, you know, we're all getting together for a little hang
就在白宫保龄球馆
at the White House bowling alley tomorrow night.
-哦 -尽情的打
- Oh - Throwing strikes
和总统一起哦
with the President of the United States.
-那可是梦寐以求的保龄球 -我可没说她会...
- That's bucket list bowling. - I didn't mean that she would...
和总统一对一面谈那真是太棒了
A one-on-one with the president would be great.
-还有拍照 -你想要照片么
- And a photographic record of it... - You want to get a photo?
我们要确认一下日程安排 -不 我们来安排
- We'd have to check with the scheduler. - No, we got this.
她可能也打得不咋地
She's probably not a very good bowler.
你可能有机会打败她呢
You might even be able to beat her.
我们肯定有印第安裔的工作人员
We do have Native American staff.
他们就在名单里 你30分钟内给我找出来 明白?
They're on a list that you're gonna give me in 30 minutes, okay?
美国拓荒时期以印第安人头皮数量领赏金
现在给我弄点头皮 名字 弄点名字来
Now get me some scalps. Names. Get me some names.
嗨 伙计 我都不知道说什么好
Hey, buddy, I don't know what to say.
这工作是我的一切
This job's my whole life.
我本不想说 但是你能帮帮我么
Hey, I hate to ask, but would you mind helping me out?
你能告诉媒体 Bill Ericsson要取代你的工作么?
Would you tell the media that Bill Ericsson's taking your job?
这样看起来会比较友善啦
It would just make it seem more amicable.
你能为我做这个么
Would you do that for me?
不
No.
如果我们可以为对话定下个时间表
And if we could just agree to a timetable for the talks.
你们能想象么 我是说这就像是为和平之墙
Can you imagine that? I mean,it would be the first brick
-加上第一块砖 - 不是墙  夫人
- in the wall of peace. - It's not a wall, ma'am.
啊 就是个表达方式  我是想说 和平之桥
Well, it's an expression. A bridge of peace, I'll say.
就快要实现了 就快了
We're so close. We're so close.
所以就是连接我的国家和想摧毁它的人们的桥?
So is my country to lots of people who would like to destroy it.
呃...
Uh...
那些纸条是关于印第安油画的事么?
Are all these notes about the Native American painting?
你在这儿说什么侵略的事
Yes, it's ironic that you're talking to us about occupation
自己还霸着别人的大陆真是讽刺啊
while you occupy someone else's continent.
好 我明白你为啥说讽刺
Yeah, okay. Well, I do see the irony in that.
不好意思 就一会儿 不好意思
Excuse me just two seconds. I'm sorry. Pardon me.
-嗨 -是关于画的
- Hi. - It's about the painting.
好 你看到我后面正发生什么事了么?
Okay, you see what's going on over here behind me?
-摊上大事了 -对
- Kind of a big deal. - Yeah.
为啥你不告诉印第安小朋友
So why don't you tell Sacheen Littlefeather
闭上嘴别bb这事儿就这么算了 好吗
to get off the rag and get over it, all right?
-好的 -还有我从来没说过刚才那些话
- Okay. - And I never said that.
-好的 -好的
- Right. - Right. Okay.
再次重申 那幅油画并未被移走
To reiterate, the painting was not removed.
只是被拿出去做清洁了
It was just taken out to be cleaned.
那是四年前才画的 怎么弄脏的?
It was painted four years ago. What made it so dirty?
就是个预防性的清洁
This was just a preemptive cleaning,
跟果汁排毒似的
much like a juice cleanse.
但是印第安油画是唯一一副被拿去排毒的?
But the Native American painting is the only one getting the cleanse?
别的油画也将被排毒
Other paintings will also be cleansed.
排毒不太准确
Cleansed is not the right word.
抹干净 不 不是抹干净
Wiped. No, not wiped.
清洁
Cleaned.
说到今晚的国宴
Moving on to the state dinner this evening.
-Sue. Sue, Sue, Sue. -什么?
- Sue. Sue, Sue, Sue. - Yeah?
我需要帮助 -帮什么
- I need your help. - What is it?
Sue我需要一扇窗户来...哇哦
Sue, I need a window for the... whoa.
Gary 你白的跟日光灯管一样
Gary, you look whiter than a Georgia country club.
-啥? -你特么怎么了?Gary?
- What?- What the hell is wrong, Gary?
我是说现在 我们没时间听你慢慢编故事
I mean currently. We don't have time for the whole tapestry.
我移的画 我干的
I moved the painting. I did it.
-你必须告诉她 -不不不 比那还糟糕
- You have to tell her. - No, no, no, it's worse than that.
-我做了件特别糟糕的事 -有孩子失踪了?
- I did something really bad. - Is there a child missing?
我想让她的第一次国宴特别棒
I wanted her first state dinner to be really nice.
你干了啥?交了脱衣舞娘?
So you what? Hired strippers?
不 我花了些钱 就是 花了一大笔钱
No, I spent some money.Like, I spent a lot of money.
哦 你真的需要告诉她
Oh, you really need to tell her.
Sue 你知道 ...你知道这不容易
Sue, you know... you know it's not as easy as that.
Gary 心中的小屁孩也该长大成熟了
Gary, your inner child needs to grow an outer man.
我只是想让她开心
Okay, I was just trying to make her happy.
任务达成 伙计
Mission incomplete, dude.
我感觉好多了
I feel so much better.
-真心感谢 心-连-心 - 棒 棒 哒
- Thank you so much. Heart-to-heart. - Great. Great.
老天 以色列的和平 印第安的战争
Boy, at peace with Israel, at war with Native Americans.
你知道我是啥? 我就是梅尔吉布森(反犹)的反义词
Do you know what I am? I'm like the opposite of Mel Gibson.
-夫人 沙特人已经不耐烦了 -哦 你应该拖住他们
- Well, ma'am, the Saudis are getting anxious. - Oh, you got to stall them.
-总统女士 我想 -对了Bill
- Madam President, I thought... - Yeah, Bill...
夫人 美国禽类协会正在担心
Ma'am, the US Poultry Association is concerned
没有您近期吃鸡蛋的照片
that there are no current photos of you eating eggs.
-棒极了 -嗨 夫人 能耽误您一会儿么
- That's terrific. - Hey, ma'am, can I just have a moment of your time?
不 我没有一会儿能让你耽误
No, I can't give you any little moment.
总统女士  我有GDP数据
Madam President, I have the GDP figures.
呃 把它交给Kent Kent你要什么
Uh, give them to Kent. Kent, what do you need?
我就是要GDP数据
I was gonna ask for the GDP figures.
-完美 -我要一丢丢时间
- Then that's perfect. - All I need is just one little second.
Gary 当我真正在吃晚宴的时候
Gary, I am going to think about the dinner
我自然我会考虑晚宴的
when I'm actually putting the dinner in my mouth.
现在我们需要的正是一些丑得掉渣的
Now what we need is a lot more butt-ugly
印第安油画 好吧
Native American paintings, okay?
因为第一张丑掉渣被某些
Because the first butt-ugly one was removed
脑子里只剩毛的混蛋移走了
by some jerkoff with a hair ball for a brain.
-好的 -现在 我要去厕所
- Yeah. - Now, I have got to go to the toilet.
所以 我希望所有人都没问题了
So I hope that can answer anybody else's questions.
我要去..哇哦
I gotta... wow.
我们建议的是 议员女士 关于这个家庭第一提案
And what we're proposing, Congresswoman, with the Families First bill...
我来讲 我来讲
No, I got this. I got this.
我们提议的是 所有提供者都有至少为十二个月的合法期
What we're proposing is a minimum 12-month eligibility period
及安全性检查
and a safety check on all providers.
我听到你说的了, 但是我想就这个提案问个技术性问题
I hear you, but I wanted to ask a technical question about the bill.
行啊 好 绝对 问吧
Sure, yeah, absolutely. Go ahead.
为什么第二章第三节
Why do title 2, section 3
第8章第5节是彼此矛盾的?
and title 8, section 5 contradict each other?
呃 我同事Egan先生 更加严谨一些
Uh, my colleague Mr. Egan, he's more the nuts and bolts guy.
-所以就让.. -不不不 你来讲
- So I'll... - No. No, no, you got this.
-不 你讲...-我们都叫他小细节
- No, you can... - We call him Dr. Details.
你喜欢马丁斯科塞么?
Do you like Martin Scorsese?
白宫即将举行他新电影的
Because we have a private screening of his new film
私人放映会
at the White House coming up.
好 他本人会到场么?
Okay. Will he be there?
是的
Yes.
哦 你的助手有东西给你
Oh, your assistant has something for you.
抱歉
Excuse me.
什么斯克塞的电影 -不造啊
- What Scorsese film? - I don't know.
他反正会出个新电影的是吧 他这么高产
He's got to have a new one dropping, right? He's really prolific.
我的上帝啊 你不能撒谎啊 Jonah
Jesus Christ. You can't lie, Jonah.
A 她会发现你说谎 B你撒谎撒的实在不咋地
A she's gonna find out B you suck at it.
你有一个团队在给你做简报 Dan
Well, you have an entire team briefing you, Dan.
你有你的Dan芙蓉和Dan凤姐
You got all your Danettes and your Dangelinas.
我可是单打独斗 我是他妈的独行侠
I'm flying solo. I'm fucking Amelia Earhart
可我还是干的比你好
and I'm still doing a better job than you.
-你还欠我一个下属 -下属?
- And you owe me a staff. - Staff?
好啊 我猜你会见到他们的
Oh, well, I guess you'll meet them all
在你瞎编的斯克塞电影里
at the Scorsese screening you're having in your head.
好啊 我猜我就去告诉大家
Oh, well, I guess I'll just start telling people
是你编造了Danny Chung受俘谣言
that you're the one that planted the Danny Chung torture rumors.
-你他妈的闭嘴 -哦 我他妈的闭嘴?
- You shut the fuck up. - Oh, me shut the fuck up?
对不起
I am sorry.
在我的选区有很多纳瓦霍族印第安人
There's a lot of Navajo in my district.
这个油画的事闹大了
This painting thing is escalating.
恐怕我要推后我们的会面了
I'm afraid I'll have to postpone.
完全理解 再联络
We completely understand. We'll be in touch.
马丁电影的事
About that screening with Marty...
你看过喜剧之王么
you ever see "The King of Comedy"?
-没有 -好片子 冷门佳作
- I haven't. - It's a good one. Underrated.
嗨 给我看看你和Kent
Hey, so let me see the photo face
努力打造的上镜脸
that you and Kent were working on.
这个不妙
That's not good.
你在撑鼻孔
You're flaring your nostrils.
-自然就这样了 -这么着吧 你看我
- It feels natural. - I'll tell you what. You watch me.
看你能不能模仿这个 好吗?
See if you can mimic this, okay?
就像... 多些这个..就像
Like... more like this. Like...
看到了么
You see that?
就是这样 宝贝儿 不不 这很好
That's right, honey. No, no, that was good.
这样看起来很开心 即使你并不开心
That looked happy, even if you're not happy.
这就是诀窍
That's the trick.
你得保证她这儿的高度
You got to make sure she has height here.
多点发量 她这儿的头比较塌
A lot of volume because her skull is low.
跟凹进去一块似的
It's kind of indented.
芭芭拉史翠珊不来晚宴了
Barbra Streisand pulled out of the state dinner.
你有萨拉希尔曼的联络方式么
Do you have Sarah Silverman's contact information?
-来参加晚宴? 没 -我想如果白宫外面有
- For the dinner? No. - I think if there are three whole flower trucks
三辆花车的话 我会知道的
parked outside the White House, I would know about it.
快去 外面 数数花车
Go. Outside, go. Count the flower trucks.
你给我找到了办公室了么
Did you find me an office?
不 但我帮你顺来这把椅子
No, but I scouted you this chair.
如果你站上去像这样 你就找到信号了
And if you stand on it just like so, you can get Wi-Fi.
-你都不能相信我今天经历了什么 -遭透了
- You would not believe the day that I'm having. - Oh, what a day.
我感到这将是我回忆录中关键的一幕了
I feel like this is gonna be a key scene in my biopic.
嗨 我要件衬衫 这不是在拍虎胆龙威
Hey, I need a shirt. This isn't "Die Hard."
嗨 甜小奶 你把规则委员会迷得晕头转向了么
Hey, sugar tits, did you stroke and choke the rules committee?
哦 当然了 Egan捅了点篓子
Oh, yeah, absolutely. Egan dropped the ball a little bit,
但是我补救了 他是个好孩子
but I picked it up. He's a good kid.
那边的天才小少年怎么样
How's it going with Mr. Genius Bar over there?
他很上进又勤奋又从不抱怨
He's eager and hardworking and never complains
每天晚上我都做梦淹死他
and every night I dream of drowning him.
-你想把他甩掉么? -天啊 好的
- How would you like to get rid of him? - God, yes.
Jonah 我真为你自豪 可爱的我都想把你当泡泡浴海绵捏捏捏
Jonah, I am so proud of you, I could squeeze you like a sponge in the shower.
哦 好 我跟你走
Yo, yeah. Yep, I'll come with you.
你有七条未读信息
You have seven missed messages.
要我读给你听么?我读给你听
Should I read 'em to you? I'll read 'em to you. Oh.
呃 Jonah 你看, Amy告诉我Richard的事
Uh, Jonah, look, Amy was telling me all about Richard here.
Richard是助理的助理
Richard apparently is the assistant's assistant.
你是说 他就是一个简易助手
Does that mean, like, he's the epitome of an assistant
-还是他是助理的助手 -第一个
- or he's just an assistant's assistant? - The first one.
Richard 你觉得就在白宫
Richard, how would you like to work right here
为Jonah Ryan工作怎么样?
in the White House for the Jonah Ryan?
-在白宫工作? -对
- Work in the White House? - Yeah.
这是在开玩笑么? 这是在整我么?
Am I being "Punk'd"? Is this hazing?
我兄弟就被整过 他处理得不太好
Happened to my brother once. He did not handle it well.
行了 Jonah 就这样吧
All right, well, Jonah, there you go.
现在你下面有人了
You now have someone under you.
太棒了 或者至少在我和Teddy之间
Great, or at least between me and Teddy.
- 嗯?
- Hmm?
-欢迎加入 -谢谢你 先生
- Welcome aboard.- Thank you, sir.
哦 先生 喜欢这个叫法 我的适应适应
Oh, "sir." I like that. I'll get used to that.
-接着叫啊 -好的先生
- Keep doing it. - Yes, sir.
又来了 叫两回了 跟我走吧
There it is again. That's twice. Come with me.
谢谢 欠你个人情
Thank you. I owe you one.
你当然欠我 不然我干嘛干这事
Of course you do. Why else would I have done it?
Gary 在干吗? 累死美国么?
What's Gary doing? Trying to max out America?
哇喔 还真有人用阿凡达钛来做灯罩?
Wow, who knew they made lampshades out of unobtanium?
好了 关于我的朋友Gary的坏话我一律没听到
Okay, guys, I will not hear a single bad word about my friend Gary.
但是 他确实有点失控了
But, no. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, he's out of control.
你看到晚宴的开销了么?
Did you see the cost of the dinner?
这会让我们难堪 让我们显得糜烂又高高在上
This'll sting us, make us look decadent and remote.
这话是从穿华伦天奴礼服的普林斯顿毕业生嘴里说的
Yeah, said the Princeton grad in the Valentino tux.
总统需要知道么?
Does the president need to know?
她盘子里已经放不下了 不是故意双关的
She's got a lot on her plate right now, no pun intended.
她这个中间人花起钱来好像巴比伦王? 还是该告诉她
That her bagman spends like a Babylonian king? Yes, I think so.
你去告诉她 她喜欢你
You can tell her. She likes you.
我没打算告诉她 你想说你去说
And I plan on keeping it that way, so I'll leave it to you.
Sue 你可以去告诉总统么
Sue, would you like to tell the president?
我不去 谢谢你还惦记着我
No, I would not, but thank you for thinking of me.
你跟总统关系不错 不是么?
You have a pretty good relationship with the president, don't you?
-你去说说 -按键按键 你好啊?
- You guys talk. - Beep, boop, beboop. Hello?
好的
Yeah, hi.
你现在在J小分队了 这些走廊都是我们的地盘
You are in the J-Corps now and we own these hallways.
-嗨 小屁孩 -耶 你妈炸了
- Hey, Preppy Longstocking. - Yeah, your fat mama.
看到没
See that?
在白宫这"翼"我们就这么做事的
It's kind of how we do things here in "the Wing."
穿过这扇门就是总统办公室
Now through this door is the Oval Office.
-蒙我吧你就 -是真的
- Fudge me. No. - Yeah.
你是我见过最狂拽酷炫的人了
You are like the coolest guy I've ever met.
总统和我 我俩就像这样
The president and I, we're like this.
-你懂的 抽象了点 -是啊
- You know, not to scale, obviously. - Of course.
谢谢
Thank you.
啊 这是叹为观止
Ah, this is truly spectacular.
谢谢 我觉得也是
Thank you. I think so.
天 我希望你没有什么过敏的
God, I hope you don't have any allergies, though,
这些花束可真是壮观啊 是不是?
'cause these centerpieces are kind of imposing, aren't they?
最好别有啥照片泄露 我看美国的媒体啊
Better not leak any photos. I see your media
最喜欢在你花了多少钱上大惊小怪
likes to make a big fuss about how much you spend.
哦 是啊
Oh, yeah.
是啊 是啊 啥?
Yes. Yes. Huh?
啥?啥大惊小怪?花啥钱?
What? What fuss? What spending?
是说晚宴么? 谁弄得?Patty?
Is it the state dinner? What, is it Patty?
-不是Patty -那是谁
- It's not Patty. - What is it?
-是Gary -Gary?
- It's Gary. - Gary?
对 他一直在挥金如土
Yeah, he's been on a spender bender.
他花了多少钱?
How much has he spent?
想象一下猫王有天觉得自己挺有钱的
Well, imagine Elton John on a day he feels fat.
媒体还在抓着那油画的事紧咬不放
Press just kept sniffing around after the stink about the painting.
顺便一提 我们要不要追究谁把画移走了?
Did we ever find out who movedthat painting, by the way?
呃 那估计也是Gary干的
Um, that would be Gary, too.
所以我刚刚和以色列达成
So I have just brokered a peace deal
和平协议
with Israel here.
我 美利坚合众国总统
I, as President of the United States,
终于做出点成就
have actually achieved something,
-还没人听说 -对
- which is virtually unheard of. - Yeah.
然后我就要跟什么油画分头条
And yet I'm sharing headline news with a painting
就因为那边的那个家伙?
because of that guy right there?
-对 - 好 我明白了
- Yep.- Okay, got it.
非常感谢
Thank you very much.
谢谢 谢谢
Thank you. Thank you.
谢谢你们
Thank you.
总理Ben-Haim
Prime Minister Ben-Haim,
Ben-Haim夫人
Mrs. Ben-Haim,
白宫欢迎你们
welcome to the White House.
仇恨是种强大的情感
Hatred is a powerful emotion.
但不是最强大的
But not the most powerful.
希望比仇恨要强大得多
Hope is more powerful than hate.
希望能够成就大业
Hope can build.
但为了燃起希望 首先我们需要信任
But for hope to grow, we first need trust,
不是么
don't we?
借用一位前总统的话来说
To paraphrase a predecessor of mine,
我们无可信任 除了信任本身
we have nothing to trust but trust itself.
Gary?
Gary!
-从那出来 -夫人 如果你听我解释
- Come out of there. - Ma'am, if you'll just let me explain.
给我出来
Come out here now.
你以为你是谁啊  Gary Antoinette?
Who do you think you are, Gary Antoinette?
你是第一夫人吗?
Did somebody make you first lady?
我可不记得我去了你啊 Gary
'Cause I don't remember marrying you, Gary.
我不记得我在尼亚加拉大瀑布操过你
I don't remember fucking you in Niagara Falls.
要是有我肯定能记住
I think I'd remember that.
夫人 油画的事我很抱歉
Ma'am, I'm really sorry for the painting
花钱的事我也很抱歉
and I'm really sorry for the spending,
-但是你必须要理解...-哦你给我闭嘴
- but you have to understand... - Oh, shut up.
给我闭嘴
Just shut up.
你不重要 好吗?
You are unimportant, okay?
你紧紧巴住我不放
And you have suckered onto me
跟车窗上的吸盘加菲猫玩具似的
like some sort of a car window Garfield.
夫人 这不是事实
That is not true, ma'am.
你以为你是这儿的大杀器么?
You think you're some sort of a big shot here?
哦 我的天啊 你不是什么大杀器 Gary
Oh, my God, you are not a big shot, Gary.
你就是一个给我的眉毛夹消毒的中年男人
You're a middle-aged man who sanitizes my tweezers.
-天啊 -你错了
- God. - You're wrong.
-你说啥? -Catherine生日是哪天?
- Excuse me? - When's Catherine's birthday?
-6月8 -9号
- June eighth. - Ninth.
-9号 -哪位参议员的女儿在戒毒?
- Ninth. - Which senator's daughter is in rehab?
-你玩的过头了 小姐 -Geldray
- You're out of line, missy. - Geldray.
-你明天要穿什么? -我不知道
- What are you wearing tomorrow? - I don't know.
我知道 我是你的日程表
I do. I'm your calendar,
我是你的谷歌 我是你的幸运球
I'm your Google, I'm your Wilson the volleyball.
-不 你不是 -是的 我是!
- No, you're not. - Yes, I am!
-不 你不是! -我为了你伤筋动骨
- No, you're not! - I have broken my body for you.
-哦得了吧 -我让自己受人嘲笑
- Oh, come on. - I have let myself be laughed at.
我让自己受尽屈辱
I have let myself be humiliated.
-但我乐意 -好的
- But I'm happy to do it. - Okay.
你大多数时候都意识不到我的存在
Most of the time you don't even know that I exist,
但我他妈的是你的一切!
but I am fucking everything to you!
哦 我很乐意换个人
Oh, I am so happy to get somebody else
来递我的护手霜
to give me my hand cream.
-好 去吧 -好
- Okay, go. - Yeah.
你能找到任何人做我做过的事么?
Can you find somebody else who did what I did?
-你是说劳动节的事么 -我没说那个
- You mean on Labor Day? - I didn't say that.
不 你说了 你刚说了
Yeah, you did. You just did.
你 你刚说了劳动节
You j... you just said Labor Day.
我说过我再也不想提起那件事了
I said I would never mention that, ever.
哦 天啊
Oh, God.
好 你看 我..
Okay, look, I'm, uh...
很抱歉我失控了
I'm sorry if I lost my temper a little bit.
很抱歉我刚才说的那些话
I am so sorry for the words that I just spoke.
你知道 在...在一段关系里...
You know, in... In a relationship...
最好把我想说的解释清楚
It's just good to clear the air is what I mean to say.
-对 我想任何的关系...-对 应该这样
- Yeah, I think any relationship... - Yeah, should do that.
-你知道 时不时的 -对对对
- You know, from time to time. - Yeah, yeah, yeah.
那看起来不错
That looks good.
对 有点 有点太泡了
Yeah, it's... It's light sponge.
你想来一块么
Would you like a piece?
-好的 我来一块 -好的 夫人
- Okay, I'll have a piece, I guess. - Yes, ma'am.
-有点泡了 -你刚说了
- It's light sponge. - You just told me that.
嗯 嗯
Mm-hmm.
Geldray的女儿在戒毒?
Geldray's daughter is in rehab?
是的
Yes.
怪不得他那么大脾气
That explains all that energy.
-特别大脾气 -对
- Lot of energy.- Right.
哇哦 这是有点泡
Wow, this is a light sponge.
嗨 Mike
Hey, Mike.
-嗨 这应该就是所有的了 -谢谢
- Hey. That should be all of them. - Thanks.
我能帮您做什么么?
Is there something I can help you with?
-呃 不 - 没有么?
- Uh, no.- No?
我就是觉得这些画特别有启发性 真心的
I just find these paintings to be inspirational. I really do.
我特别喜欢这颜色
I particularly love this color here.
真是可爱极了 不是么?
I think this is so pretty, don't you?
这幅画标题是大屠杀
I believe the title is "Massacre."
为你们颁发团队庆贺奖牌的是
And giving you your Celebrating Community medals
美利坚合众国第一女儿 Catherine Meyer
is the First Daughter of the United States, Catherine Meyer.
天 你可真小
My, you are small.
我猜你很小 不过你还是真是小个子
I suppose you're young, but you're still very small.
亲爱的 别看起来怪怪的 我又不会咬你
Honey, don't look so worried. I'm not gonna bite you.
但那别的那个男人有枪哦
But that man over there does have a gun.
你女儿的这张照片拍的真好
That's a wonderful photo of your daughter.
是的 她看起来真讨喜 不是么
Yeah, she looks so loveable there, don't you think?
非常 非常讨喜
Very... well, she looks likable.
你觉得她在照片里讨喜么
Do you think she looks likable in that picture?
你看过星球大战么?
Have you ever seen "Star Wars"?
这有点像星球大战的结尾
This is a little bit like the end of "Star Wars."
整个国家的人民向你感谢你的服务
The whole country thanks you for your service.
-夫人 -什么?
- Ma'am.- Yeah?
南韩打电话了
South Korea has called.
他们想知道你喜不喜欢大象宝宝
They'd like to know if you'd like a baby elephant.
没什么好说的
I have no response to that.
除了 我已经有一个了
Other than I already have one.
我开玩笑的啦
I'm kidding.
她小时候胖乎乎的
She used to be chubby when she was little,
不过长大后就瘦多了
but she's slimmed down as she's gotten older.
谢天谢地啊
Thank goodness.
非常好 非常好
Very good, very good.
谢谢
Thank you.
你能想办法让我合理的离开这么
Can you pull me out the second it become acceptable to leave?
嗯 嗯
Mm-hmm.